intelliad.com 2012-10-17

# Privacy Policy - intelliAd Media GmbH

Privacy Policy

## Last updated: 06/2012

Our Online Privacy Statement is designed to inform you about our collection and use of personal information on this web site. From time to time, intelliAd Corporation (referred to in this policy as "intelliAd") may modify this Online Privacy Statement.

The Online Privacy Statement is available on the home page of this web site as well as at every point on the web site where you provide us with personal information.

This privacy policy only applies to the information we collect on the intelliAd.de website. This privacy policy does not apply to information we collect through other methods or sources, including sites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors or partners.

### 1\. The Only Personal Information We Collect Online is Information You Voluntarily Provide to Us.

The only information we collect about you on this web site is information that you voluntarily provide to us. This information may include, for example, name, mailing address, email address, phone number and similar information. If you supply us with personal information on this web site, we will use that information only to contact you so that we can:

  * provide you with the information you have requested (press releases, investor information)
  * follow up on job opportunities that you have inquired about, or
  * occasionally send you other information about intelliAd and its services that we believe you would find interesting.

This information will not be sent to you via email unless you ask us to do so. 

### 2\. When You Browse the intelliAd Web Site, You Do So Without Revealing Your Identity.

This intelliAd web site may use cookies to aggregate information about the pages that users visit so that we can update and redesign, as necessary, our web site in order to provide you with the most useful information. Personal information, such as your email address, is not collected, unless you provide it to us. intelliAd does not disclose domain name or aggregate information to third parties other than vendors who assist us with our web site and who are under strict confidentiality requirements. From time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or regulatory obligations or if we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our rights, the rights of others, or to prevent harm. In addition, we may aggregate data about users of our site and use it for statistical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our site’s users and how to improve our site and our offerings.

### 3\. We Are Committed to Protecting the Confidentiality of User Information.

intelliAd's policies limit access to personal user information that is collected from this web site to those employees of intelliAd and its affiliates and business partners who need the information to fulfill their business responsibilities. A transfer of your personal information to third parties is not made without your necessary consent. The transmission of personal information to authorized federal institutions and authorities is only proceeded according to applicable laws or if we are obliged to do so by a legal decision. Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements to ensure that personal information is safeguarded. Employees and others with duties related to this web site must adhere to this Online Privacy Statement. Any employee violating this Online Privacy Statement may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal.

As noted above, from time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or regulatory obligations or if we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our rights, the rights of others, or to prevent harm. In addition, we may aggregate data about users of our site and use it for statistical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our site’s users and how to improve our site and our offerings.

### 4\. Collected Data for Web Tracking

In the course of tracking, we collect and analyze some information for our web controlling. This information is transmitted by your browser. The data collection is processed by a pixel which is integrated on every web page. The following data are collected automatically: - Request (Data name of requested file) (Example www.example.com/index.html) – Browser type/version (Example: Internet Explorer 6.0) – Browser language (Example: German) – Used operating system (Example: Windows XP) – Inner resolution of browser window – display resolution – Javascript activation – Java On/Off – Cookies On/Off – Color Depth – Referer URL (the site visited before) – IP address – is anonymized and deleted instantly – Time of access – Clicks –Order values, if necessary.

### 5\. IP Address

The IP address is transmitted at every server request, so that the server knows where the corresponding answer needs to be sent. The IP address is provided by an Internet Service Provider (ISP) as soon as a user connects with the internet and the ISP can understand which IP address is assigned to which client at a certain time. As long as the IP address is stored, the identity of the user can theoretically be determined via the ISP. Therefore, we save the IP address in (anonymized) form and only use them to recognize the session, for geo-localization (until city –level) and for the defense of attacks. The IP address is deleted instantly so that the collected data are anonymous and the identification of the user’s identity via ISPs is no longer possible.

### 6\. Cookies and Clear GIFs

 **What are Cookies?**

Cookies are data files that are placed on the internet user’s PC by webservers and save basic information (for example user interests). The use of cookies on this site offers users a user-friendly visit based on the measurement of the user behavior on the site. There are two types of cookies: session-cookies and persistent cookies. Session-cookies are only available during the online session of an internet user. They disappear from the user’s PC as soon as the user closes the browser software. Persistent cookies stay on the user’s PC even if the browser is closed. The cookies used on the intelliAd site are not individual-related. They only recognize the user’s browser. The following cookies are used by intelliAd: - Last Click (for session timeout, lifetime: one session) – Session Cookie (for session recognition, lifetime: one session) – Ever-Cookie (for recognition of new/steady customers).

### 7\. Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

### 8\. Opt-Out & Update Policy

intelliAd offers its website’s visitors the opportunity to control the use of their session data. If you registered at or ordered services from intelliAd (“Services”), but do not wish to receive any more information from us afterwards or changed your opinion about the use of your optional information, please let us know about your new choice. If you would also like to prevent intelliAd from collecting and analyzing your session data while visiting our website, you can unsubscribe through the opt-out option at <http://login.intelliad.de/optout.php?locale=en> so that all site usage data within intelliAd are deleted.

### 9\. We Give Web Site Users a Choice about How Their Information Will be Used.

In some instances, if we collect information online, we will inform users at that point about how to remove their names from our lists. You can request access to the information we hold about you at any time by contacting us at intelliAd Media, Sendlinger Str. 7, 80331 Munich, Germany or by emailing us at info(at)intelliad.de

### 10\. We Use Appropriate Security Safeguards

At intelliAd, security is a priority. intelliAd employs appropriate measures, including advanced technology, to protect personal information collected online against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These measures may include, among others, encryption, physical access security, and other appropriate technologies. intelliAd continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.

### 12\. intelliAd's Web Site May Be Linked to Other Web Sites.

As you navigate our site, you may click to web sites of our different subsidiaries and divisions. Those web sites may have their own online privacy statements or policies. This Online Privacy Statement will not apply when you move to one of these other sites because business unit privacy practices and policies are tailored to the products and services offered by the individual intelliAd business units. As you visit the pages and sites of our different business units please be sure to review the privacy policies applicable to those sites.

intelliAd may create links to third-party web sites. intelliAd is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by web sites that are linked to our web site.

### Final Note

For more information on this subject please contact our **data protection** **officer** :

intelliAd Media  
Michael Schunke  
Sendlinger Str. 7  
80331 München  
T: +49 (0)89 / 15 90 490 - 51  
E: Michael.Schunke(at)intelliad.de
